ACTWU's Organizing Department Records. 5619/007
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Weekly Organizing Report, 1982 (Box 60, Folder 20)
  B. Fox; R. Gay; V. Hines; V. Keyser; R. Manini; A. Miceli; G. Mikula; R. Mullins
- Quin State. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 21)
  J. Coury; R. Harris
- Quin State. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 60, Folder 22)
  Tom Hummel
- Master Agreement between Armour and Co. and AMCBW, 1976-1979 (Box 61, Folder 1)
- Form 10-K. The Greyhound Corp., 1978-1979 (Box 61, Folder 2)
- The Greyhound Lines, Inc and the Amalgamated Council of Greyhound Local Unions, 1977-1980 (Box 61, Folder 3)
- Greyhound. Armour Handcrafts, 1980-1982 (Box 61, Folder 4)
- Greyhound Corp., 1977-1980 (Box 61, Folder 5)
- Armour Handcraft and Workers, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 6)
- Algo Fabrics Co., 1974 (Box 61, Folder 7)
- Webster Oxford Area Telephone Directory, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 8)
- ACTWU to Paul Swaity, 1977-1979 (Box 61, Folder 9)
- Woolen Mills, 1978-1980 (Box 61, Folder 10)
- Staff Meetings, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 11)
- Algo Fabrics, 1968-1971 (Box 61, Folder 12)
  Webster Mass
- Anglo Fabrics, 1979 (Box 61, Folder 13)
- Anglo Fabrics, 1977 (Box 61, Folder 14)
- Agreements between ACTWU and Various Companies, 1976-1981 (Box 62, Folder 1)
  Barre Plant, Dartmouth, Dorr, Charlton, and Homestead Woolen Mills, Felters, and Hayward Schuster
- Anglo Plants, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 2)
- Anglo Worker, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 3)
- Labor Agreements, 1972-1978 (Box 62, Folder 4)
- ACTWU, 1976-1980 (Box 62, Folder 5)
- Anglo Times, 1974 (Box 62, Folder 6)
- Objections to election, 1980 (Box 62, Folder 7)
- Anglo Fabrics, 1978 (Box 62, Folder 8)
- Anglo Letters, 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 9)
- Anglo ILG leaflets, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 10)
- Anglo Letters, 1979 (Box 62, Folder 11)
- Anglo Misc., 1979 (Box 62, Folder 12)
- Anglo Fabrics, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 13)
- Anglo to Misc, Union Wool Workers, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Originals, 1979-1980 (Box 62, Folder 15)
- Anglo Fabrics, 1979-1984. (Box 62, Folder 16)
- American- Olean Tile Co., 1979 (Box 62, Folder 17)
  subs. of National Gypsum Co. Lewisport and Cloverport, KY
- Waverly Textile Processing, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 1)
  Plainview, N.Y.
- Uniglas Industries, 1990-1981 (Box 63, Folder 2)
  Division of United Merchants. Statesville, NC
- United Bags, Inc, 1975-1979 (Box 63, Folder 3)
- Vinton Weaving Company, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 4)
  Division of Burlington Ind
- H. Warshaw and Sons, 1979-1981 (Box 63, Folder 5)
- H. Warshaw, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 6)
- Tilton Rack and Basket Corp., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 7)
- Trend Mills, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 8)
  Rome, GA
- Trend Mills (WWG), 1974-1980 (Box 63, Folder 9)
  Rome,GA
- Stehli Mills, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 10)
  Division of Indian Head
- Spray Textured Yarns, Inc, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 11)
  Eden,NC
- Sprayomatic Co., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 12)
  Lawrence, Mass
- Roosevelt Mills, 1976-1967 (Box 63, Folder 13)
- RYT-WAY Packaging Corp., 1981 (Box 63, Folder 14)
- Sajar Plastics, 1977-1979 (Box 63, Folder 15)
  Middlefield, Ohio
- Romespun, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 16)
- Rock-Tenn Company, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 17)
  Opelika, Alabama
- Quaker Lace, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 18)
- Quik-Set Lettering Co., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 19)
  Westerville, Ohio
- Principle Business Enterprises, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 20)
  Dunbridge, Ohio
- Prince Gardner, 1976 (Box 63, Folder 21)
- Preferred Plastics, 1976-1980 (Box 63, Folder 22)
- Pottsville Bleach and Dye, 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 23)
- Peck and Hale, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 24)
  Sayville, LI
- Pedro Mfg., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 25)
- Perfect Fit Industries, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 26)
  Monroe, North Carolina
- Peacedale Processing Co., 1981-1982 (Box 63, Folder 27)
  subs. Kenyon Piece Dye Works
- Peacedale Processing, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 28)
  Peacedale, RI
- Nuway Tobacco, 1977-1980 (Box 63, Folder 29)
  South Windsor, Conn
- Matchmaker Dyeing and Finishing, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 30)
  Los Angeles, California
- C. H. Masland and Sons, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 31)
  Lewistown, PA
- Masland Carpets, 1978-1979 (Box 63, Folder 32)
  Lewistown, Pennsylvania
- Levi Strauss, 1973-1980 (Box 63, Folder 33)
- Linn-Corriher, 1980-1982 (Box 63, Folder 34)
  Dominion Textile. Landis, NC
- Logo 7, Inc, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 35)
- Lebanon Woolen Mills, Inc, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 36)
  Lebanon, Tenn.
- Krystinel Corp., 1981 (Box 63, Folder 37)
  Paterson, NJ
- Krystenel Electronics, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 38)
- Kayser-Roth, 1971-1977 (Box 63, Folder 39)
  Dayton, Tenn. Decertification
- Kendall Mills, 1973-1976 (Box 63, Folder 40)
- Kayser-Roth, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 41)
- Harold and Jack Kahn, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 42)
- Jockey Men's Wear (Cooper), 1971-1981 (Box 63, Folder 43)
  Millen, GA.
- IMCO Container, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 44)
  Lewistown, Penn
- Chas, House and Sons, 1977-1978 (Box 63, Folder 45)
  Unionville, Conn
- Galaxy Carpets, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 46)
- Globe Mfg. Co, 1977 (Box 63, Folder 47)
  Gastonia, NC
- Frolic Footwear, 1980 (Box 63, Folder 48)
  Div. of Wolverine Worldwide, Russellville, Ark.
- Franklin IX and Sons, 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 49)
- Fieldcrest Mills, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 50)
- Fiber Industries, 1979 (Box 63, Folder 51)
  Div of Celanese. Salisbury, NC
- FMC Radford Plant, 1973-1975 (Box 63, Folder 52)
- Facetglas, Inc, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 53)
- Exxon Chemical Co., 1973-1978 (Box 63, Folder 54)
  Ribbon Fabrics Civ. Summerville SC
- Exxon Chemical Co., 1980 (Box 63, Folder 55)
  Summerville, SC
- Electronic Transformer Corp, 1978 (Box 63, Folder 56)
- Dow Badische, 1979-1980 (Box 63, Folder 57)
- Decodex Inc., 1980-1981 (Box 63, Folder 58)
  Westerly,RI
- De- Co -Art Corp, 1982 (Box 63, Folder 59)
  Washington, Ind.
- Congress Sportswear, 1981 (Box 63, Folder 60)
  Bath, Maine
- Colby Ok. Wool Co., 1981 (Box 63, Folder 61)
  Worcester, Mass
- Blank Staff Employment Application (Box 64, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Dues, 1981 (Box 64, Folder 2)
- Telephone Messages (Box 64, Folder 3)
- Blank Overtime Slips, Attendance Reports and Personnel Absentee (Box 64, Folder 4)
- Airline Ticket Requests, 1977-1984 (Box 64, Folder 5)
- Organizing Currently Supervised By, 1980 (Box 64, Folder 6)
- Organizing Documents (Box 64, Folder 7)
- ACTWU Misc Documents [1 of 4] (Box 64, Folder 8)
- ACTWU Misc. Documents [3 of 4], 1975-1977 (Box 64, Folder 9)
- ACTWU Misc. Documents [4 of 4], 1981 (Box 64, Folder 10)
- Diane Bruneau, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 11)
- Lydia Brucamonte, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 12)
- Barry John, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 13)
- Pat Cronin, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 14)
- L. A. Dunigan, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 15)
- Ronald Harris, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 16)
- Tom Hummel, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 17)
- Virginia Kayer, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 18)
- Trudy J. Khan, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 19)
- Donna Kreknik, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 20)
- Bessie Manning, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 21)
- Anthony Miceli, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 22)
- Huguette Nicol, 1985-1986 (Box 64, Folder 23)
- Erika Outland, 1985 (Box 64, Folder 24)
- Robert Petrin, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 25)
- John A. Tedesco, 1984 (Box 64, Folder 26)
- Department number for merged payroll, 1983 (Box 64, Folder 27)
- Various Documents, 1967-1978 (Box 65, Folder 1)
  Fact Sheets for Organizer. Guide for Hearing Officer in Rep. Organization and Law. Staff Kits. NLRB Field Manual and Guide. Leaflets and Pamphlets
- Address Book A-Mc, 1966-1979 (Box 65, Folder 2)
- Address Book M-Y, 1969-1982 (Box 65, Folder 3)
- Address Cards, 1970-1979 (Box 65, Folder 4)
- Address Cards, 1967-1977 (Box 65, Folder 5)
- Assignment Change and Address Cards, 1968-1978 (Box 65, Folder 6)
- Staff Manual. Compilation of Employer Material, and Communication and Persuasion, 1969-1978 (Box 65, Folder 7)
- Orders- Pamphlets, Booklets, and Ect. (Box 65, Folder 8)
- Other Unions, 1981-1983 (Box 65, Folder 9)
- Pension Reform Law, 1975 (Box 65, Folder 10)
- A. Philip Randolph Institute, 1973-1978 (Box 65, Folder 11)
- Phillip Randolph Institute, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 12)
- NLRB Model Authorization Card, 1968 (Box 65, Folder 13)
- Organizing Campaigns, 1976-1977 (Box 65, Folder 14)
  Evaluations
- Current Organizing Campaigns, 1978-1979 (Box 65, Folder 15)
- Oil, Chemical, and Atomic Workers Union, 1975-1976 (Box 65, Folder 16)
- OSHA Occupational Safety and Health Act, 1970-1982 (Box 65, Folder 17)
- Organizing General, 1978-1982 (Box 65, Folder 18)
- NLRB Proposed Changes, 1978 (Box 65, Folder 19)
- NLRB R. Excelsior Lists, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 20)
- Minimum Wage, 1972-1976 (Box 65, Folder 21)
- Miscellaneous Requests, 1977-1982 (Box 65, Folder 22)
- NIOSH, 1980 (Box 65, Folder 23)
- NLRB Misc., 1966-1983 (Box 65, Folder 24)
- Wages and Conditions in Right to Work States, 1974-1975 (Box 65, Folder 25)
- Earning Gap and Low Wages (Box 65, Folder 26)
- ACTWU Misc Documents (Box 65, Folder 27)
- Labor Laws Changes, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 1)
- Labor Law Reform, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 2)
- Institute for Southern Studies, 1977-1978 (Box 66, Folder 3)
- IAF Seminar on Organizing. Seamen's Institute Center, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 4)
  New York City. November 17-18th
- UTW, 1979-1981 (Box 66, Folder 5)
- Machine Printers Association, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 6)
- Machine Printers Union Independent, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 7)
- IUD Mississippi Project, 1974 (Box 66, Folder 8)
- IUD Coordinated Organizing Program, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  Tupilo, Mississippi
- IUD-CLUW Organizing Campaign, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 10)
  Baltimore-Washington Area
- Industrial Union Department, 1980-1983 (Box 66, Folder 11)
- IUD Atlanta Organizing Project, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 12)
- IUD Coordinated Bargaining, 1978-1980 (Box 66, Folder 13)
- IUD Study NLRB Wins vs. Contracts, 1976-1980 (Box 66, Folder 14)
- IUD Coordinated Organizing Program, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 15)
  Southwestern States
- IUD Staff Training Program, 1982 (Box 66, Folder 16)
  Atlanta, Georgia. March 22-31st
- Japanese Firms and Politics in US, 1980-1981 (Box 66, Folder 17)
- Japanese Textiles, 1972-1978 (Box 66, Folder 18)
- Lewiston Independent Textile Association, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 19)
- Looseleaf Binders, 1976-1977 (Box 66, Folder 20)
- IUD Tupelo Mississippi Project, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 21)
- Imports, 1976-1980 (Box 66, Folder 22)
- ILG (International Ladies Garment Workers Union), 1975-1983 (Box 66, Folder 23)
- Illegal Alien Immigration, 1977-1980 (Box 66, Folder 24)
- Hosiery, Mortuary and Death Benefit Funds, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 25)
- Hosiery Death Benefit Fund, 1972-1980 (Box 66, Folder 26)
- ACTWU- Sidney Hillman Foundation. Financial Reports, 1976-1982 (Box 66, Folder 27)
- Scott Hoyman: Executive Vice President, 1979-1983 (Box 66, Folder 28)
- New England. Weekly Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 29)
  C. Cassanova, G. Dion, R. Dubois
- New England. Weekly Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 30)
  J. Notarangelo; F. Rouillard; G. Thibault
- Canada. Weekly Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 31)
  W. Clarke; D. Lachapelle; M. Robillard
- Synthetic. Weekly Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 66, Folder 32)
  R. Fox;R. Gay;J. Orange; S. Sachen; L. Smalley
- Canada. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 33)
  D. Bruneau; W. Clarke; M. Robillard
- JPS. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 34)
- South. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 66, Folder 35)
- South. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 1)
- South. Weekly Organizing Report, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 2)
- J. P. Stevens, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 3)
- New York. Weekly Organizing Report, 1977 (Box 67, Folder 4)
- Quin State. Weekly Organizing Report [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 67, Folder 5)
- Quin State. Weekly Organizing Report [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 67, Folder 6)
- Quin State. Weekly Organizing Report [folder 1 of 2], 1980 (Box 67, Folder 7)
- Quin State. Weekly Organizing Report [folder 2 of 2], 1980 (Box 67, Folder 8)
- Upper South, 1981 (Box 67, Folder 9)
- South. Weekly Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 10)
- South. Weekly Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 67, Folder 11)
- Dyeing, Printing and Finishing Listed by State, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 1)
- ACTWU- Cordage and Rope Plants, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 2)
- Organized Plants in Maine, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 3)
- Hosiery Industry, 1979 (Box 68, Folder 4)
- IUD Area Coordinating Committee, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 5)
- Unorganized Industrial Plants, 1972 (Box 68, Folder 6)
- Area Specific Surveys for Charlotte, East Tennessee, and Greensboro, 1981 (Box 68, Folder 7)
- New York: Unorganized Plants of Companies under contract with ACTWU (Box 68, Folder 8)
- Targets Cleared. ACTWU Organizing Dept. (Box 68, Folder 9)
- How to Organize a Union in your Plant. They said it couldn't be done. Blank ACTWU Report (Box 68, Folder 10)
- ACTWU Report on Objections, 1980 (Box 68, Folder 11)
- ACTWU Staff Members Literature (Box 68, Folder 12)
- ACTWU- Literature. Unorganized Plants of Companies in ACTWU Jurisdiction, 1982 (Box 68, Folder 13)
- ACTWU- Readings on Social Significance. Roots of Political Behavior, 1961 (Box 68, Folder 14)
- ACTWU, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 15)
- ACTWU- Literature. Misc. Documents, 1978 (Box 68, Folder 16)
- ACTWU Fact Sheets for Organizers, 1969 (Box 68, Folder 17)
- ACTWU Literature and Guidebook (Box 68, Folder 18)
- Plant Surveys. ACTWU Director, 1979-1980 (Box 68, Folder 19)
- Newsletter-Crafted with Pride, 1985 (Box 68, Folder 20)
  March
- Newsletter. ACTWU, 1980 (Box 69, Folder 1)
- Elections, 1978 (Box 69, Folder 2)
- NLRB Election Summary. Misc. Documents, 1976-1981 (Box 69, Folder 3)
- Branch Plants of Companies with ACTWU Contracts, 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 4)
- Users of NLRB Election Histories. ACTWU Shoe and Clothing Division. Election & Recognition., 1980-1981 (Box 69, Folder 5)
- Orientation Kit for New Staff Representative (Box 69, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Unions, 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 1)
- Fact Power: Quality Circles, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 2)
- The Union's View of Industrial Engineering in the 1980's, 1979-1982 (Box 70, Folder 3)
- Newspaper clippings and Literature, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 4)
- Quality Circles, 1982 (Box 70, Folder 5)
- Labor. Work Life. National Productivity Review, 1981-1982 (Box 70, Folder 6)
- Quality Circles. General Motors Corp., 1979-1982 (Box 70, Folder 7)
  copy 1
- Quality Circles. General Motors Corp., 1979-1982 (Box 70, Folder 8)
  copy 2
- Newspaper clippings. Positive Labor Relations. National Productivity Review, 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 9)
- Union's View of Industrial Engineering in the 1980's, 1979-1982 (Box 70, Folder 10)
- Conference on Project Counter Attack. Newspaper Clippings. Bargaining and Buster, 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 11)
- List of Charles Hughes Seminar attendants. Commodities made by members of ACTWU, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 12)
- Organizing Department. Docs., 1979-1980 (Box 70, Folder 13)
- Textile Mill Productivity Docs. Surveys, 1980-1982 (Box 70, Folder 14)
- ACTWU Research and Textile Liquidation, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 15)
- NLRB Elections, 1977-1980 (Box 70, Folder 16)
- Textile Imports and Exports. JPS, 1977-1980 (Box 70, Folder 17)
- Captive Audience and Speeches. Report on Organizing Mtg., 1978-1980 (Box 70, Folder 18)
- Group Insurance Plan, 1979 (Box 70, Folder 19)
- Supervisory Talk Sheet. Speech by Vivian Greene, 1977 (Box 70, Folder 20)
- Supervisory Talk Sheets, 1981 (Box 70, Folder 21)
- ACTWU Speeches, 1977-1982 (Box 70, Folder 22)
- Organizing Department. Finance, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 1)
  Correspondence
- Organizing Department, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 2)
  Headwear Division
- Organizing Department. Blank Forms (Box 71, Folder 3)
- Organizing Dept. Elections Survey, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 4)
- Replies. Elections Survey, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 5)
- Survey Replies, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 6)
- ACTWU Elections, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 7)
- Blank ACTWU Organizing Election Reports, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 8)
- AFL-CIO IUD NLRB Election, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 9)
- Organizing Dept. IUD Election Summary, 1982 (Box 71, Folder 10)
- I. U.D.-NLRB Election Summary, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 11)
  July-December
- Organizing Department. IUD, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 12)
  McIver, Harold
- IUD Area Comm, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 13)
  March 12th. College Park, GA
- AFL-CIO Organizer Source Book, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 14)
- Organizer's Handbook (Box 71, Folder 15)
- Organizing Department. Mailings General, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 16)
- Organizing Department. Kentucky Organizing Program, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 17)
- Organizing Department. Letter with Sample Leaflets, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 18)
  Blue Book
- Organizing Department. NLRB Requests for Reports, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 19)
- NLRB. Winston Salem, NC, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 20)
  Monthly Reports
- NLRB Region 10, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 21)
  Atlanta, GA. Weekly Representation Reports
- Organizing Department, 1981-1884 (Box 71, Folder 22)
  Targets and Data
- Organizing Department, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 23)
  Southern Region- General
- Organizing Department, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 24)
  Telephone Calls
- Strike Information- BNA Report, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 25)
- AFL-CIO National Organizing Com, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 26)
  July 10th. Washington D.C.
- Organizing Department, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 27)
  9/21
- Meany Center, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 28)
  Conference Cancellation Fee
- AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 29)
  December 12th. Washington DC
- AFL-CIO National Organizing Survey, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 30)
- Organizing Department. Requests for Literature and Organizing Supplies, 1983-1986 (Box 71, Folder 31)
- Organizing Department, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 32)
  Requests from Education
- Organizing Department, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 33)
  Charter Membership Cards
- Organizing Department. Canada, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 34)
- Organizing Department, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 35)
  Bensinger, Richard and Kriksciun, Curt. November 9th
- Organizing Department, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 36)
  Authorization Card
- Alternative Forms of Membership, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 37)
- Organizing Department. Activity Report Project, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 38)
- Training Program for Organizers, 1983 (Box 71, Folder 39)
  George Meany Labor Center. Oct 2-7th
- Crystal Zoo, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 40)
- AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee Meeting, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 41)
  AFL-CIO National Organizing Committee Mtg. February 19-20th
- National Organizing Committee Mtg., 1985 (Box 71, Folder 42)
  Executive Council Rm at AFL-CIO
- AFL-CIO Organizing Committee, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 43)
  "Representation Procedures Under NLRB"
- AFL-CIO Survey, 1985 (Box 71, Folder 44)
- AFL-CIO Organizing Dept., 1985 (Box 71, Folder 45)
- Org. Dept. AFL-CIO Dept. of Organizing, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 46)
- Scott Hoyman, 1983-1985 (Box 71, Folder 47)
- Scott Hoyman, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 48)
- AFL-CIO, 1984-1985 (Box 71, Folder 49)
- AFL-CIO, 1984-1985 (Box 71, Folder 50)
- Org. Dept. Misc. Companies, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 51)
- AFL-CIO "Unicore", 1984 (Box 71, Folder 52)
  Union and Non- Union Status of Companies
- AFL-CIO: Advanced Organizing Course at Meany Center, 1984 (Box 71, Folder 53)
  March 5-15th
- AFL-CIO Organizing Dept, 1983-1984 (Box 71, Folder 54)
  Feb. 22-23 rd. Bel Harbour, Florida
- Names and Addresses of Employees (Box 72, Folder 1)
- Names and Addresses of Employees (Box 72, Folder 2)
- Names and Addresses of Employees (Box 72, Folder 3)
- Hourly Employee list by department (Box 72, Folder 4)
- Hanes Workers' Voice, 1982-1983 (Box 72, Folder 5)
- Ideas for Program, 1982-1983 (Box 72, Folder 6)
- Organizing Information about Targets, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 7)
- Greeneville, Tenn, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 8)
- Info Community Lenders, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 9)
- American Greetings Corporation, 1980-1982 (Box 72, Folder 10)
- American Greeting Corp. Information on Campaign and Plants, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 11)
- Missouri Map (Box 72, Folder 12)
- Organizing Dept. (Box 72, Folder 13)
- Union's Organizing Progress Factors. Staff Development Conference, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 14)
- L'Eggs. ACTWU. Organizing Cultural Programs for Working People (Box 72, Folder 15)
- ACTWU Staff Coordinator Development Program, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 16)
- Arrangements for Coordinated Staff Training Program, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 17)
  Dec. 13-17th. Seamen's Training Center
- Original Graphs, 1977-1982 (Box 72, Folder 18)
- Overhead Graphs, 1959-1981 (Box 72, Folder 19)
- Reg. Org. Coordinators Training Program, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 20)
  New York City. December 14-18th
- Transparent Overhead graphs of Data, 1976-1982 (Box 72, Folder 21)
- Committee on Organization Mtg. ACTWU Headquarters, 1982-1983 (Box 72, Folder 22)
  New York City. March 28th
- Staff Training Evaluation, 1973-1982 (Box 72, Folder 23)
- Revisions on Osceola Mailing List, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 24)
- The A. G. Workers' Voice, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 25)
- Union Wages and Benefits. Asceola Conditions. L'Eggs Reps Solidarity Report, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 26)
- Osceola Talking it Over, 1973-1978 (Box 72, Folder 27)
- American Greeting List, 1961-1982 (Box 72, Folder 28)
- Employee List (Box 72, Folder 29)
- Agnews, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 30)
  Copy 1
- Agnews, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 31)
- Agnews, 1982 (Box 72, Folder 32)
  copy 3
- Staff Lists (Box 72, Folder 33)
- Health Care, 1981-1982 (Box 72, Folder 34)
- Insurance Pension Fund, 1983 (Box 72, Folder 35)
- Osceola Factory. Blank ACTWU Organizing Report, 1980 (Box 72, Folder 36)
- ACTWU. Labor Center. Apparel Industry. Misc. Notes, 1990 (Box 73, Folder 1)
- ACTWU Sourcebook (Box 73, Folder 2)
- Coordinated Staff Reports on Assignments, 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 3)
- Coordinators Training Program, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 4)
  George Meany Center. May 1-6
- Staff Coordinator Training Institute, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 5)
  George Meany Labor Center
- The INC. 500, 1983 (Box 73, Folder 6)
- Handwritten Notes. Staff Development Conference, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 7)
- Caron Intl. Plan Outline. Misc. ACTWU documents, 1980-1983 (Box 73, Folder 8)
- Statistics. Pension Plan. Settlement, 1972-1981 (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Staff Development Conference, 1980 (Box 73, Folder 10)
  3 copies
- Plus Mark. Addresses. Plan Outline, 1982-1983 (Box 73, Folder 11)
- Blank ACTWU Survey on Proposed New Org. (Box 73, Folder 12)
- Competitive Card Companies, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 13)
- Data on Organizing. Profiles. Handwritten Notes, 1981 (Box 73, Folder 14)
- Handwritten Notes. Staff Training Program, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 15)
- Graphic Arts, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 16)
  Osceola, Arkansas
- Staffing. Newspaper Clippings. Organizing Dept., 1977-1982 (Box 73, Folder 17)
- Misc. Documents. Arkansas Maps. Objectives. Highlights, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 18)
- Testimony before House Congressional Committee, 1977 (Box 73, Folder 19)
- Agnews, 1982 (Box 73, Folder 20)
- Cornwall Joint Board, 1978-1984 (Box 74, Folder 1)
  Discussion of Full Service Manager
- Local 1332. Cornwall Loan. Canada, 1976-1978 (Box 74, Folder 2)
- Greater Toronto Joint Board, 1960-1987 (Box 74, Folder 3)
- Greater Toronto Joint Board. Annual Dinner and Dance, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 4)
  March 26th
- Canada. Montreal Joint Board, 1982 (Box 74, Folder 5)
- Canada. Jean-Marc Couture, 1976-1987 (Box 74, Folder 6)
- Canada. Quebec Joint Board General, 1976-1985 (Box 74, Folder 7)
- Canada. Eastern Townships, 1975-1976 (Box 74, Folder 8)
- J. V. Components, 1979 (Box 74, Folder 9)
  St. Therese
- Canada. Quebec Joint Board Bills for first Contract, 1979-1982 (Box 74, Folder 10)
- Quebec Joint Board. 20th Anniversary Banquet, 1987 (Box 74, Folder 11)
  April 25th
- Canada. Quebec Province. Language Law and Translations, 1976-1983 (Box 74, Folder 12)
- Canada. Southwestern Ontario Joint Board, 1978-1987 (Box 74, Folder 13)
- Joint Board's Annual Banquet, 1983 (Box 74, Folder 14)
- Southwestern Ontario Board, 1981 (Box 74, Folder 15)
- Sam Fox Retirement Dinner, 1986 (Box 74, Folder 16)